picroma.com 2012-04-17

# Privacy Policy

### Acquisition, Processing and Usage of Personal Information

Protecting your personal data is of particular importance to us. In order to visit our website you don't have to provide any personal data. Solely anonymous access data not being related to any personal information is logged. Storage of this data serves technical and statistical purposes. For each request on our server, the file name, date and time, transferred size and success status is logged, as well as browser and operating system identification, referrer URL and your IP address. We are not able to assign this information to specific individuals. 

We collect personal data only if you provide it by choice during account registration or order transaction. We use the collected data exclusively for contract fulfilment and technical administration. We do not share any personal data with third parties for any reason. 

### Data Security

Our websites and databases are protected against damage, deletion and unauthorized access by technical and organizational means. SSL encryption is applied during data transmission to provide a secure and reliable safeguard against access by third parties. Since we cannot ensure complete protection for Email communication, we recommend sending us confidential information by mail. 

### Right of Information and Withdrawal

On demand, we will provide you with information of your stored data free of charge. You can make us block, correct or delete your stored data at any time. You can always withdraw your agreement to our privacy policy and thus cancel your Picroma user account. 

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy is subject to change and we will post any significant changes on our website. Your continued use of our website after such changes have been posted shall constitute your acceptance thereof.
